Humane Borders records, 2000-2010 MS 471
University of Arizona
- Series I: Media Files, 2000-2010
  - Subseries 1: News clippings, June 1, 2000-December 29, 2009
    - Disciple World, June 1, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Green Valley News, June 1, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Yuma Sun, June 2, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 9, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 9, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 10, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - AZfamily.com, June 10, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 9, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - KMSB, June 10, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 10, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Arizona Republic, June 11, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 11, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Arizona Star, June 11, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - New York Times, June 11, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Arizona Star, June 11, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 11, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 11, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Salt Lake Tribune, June 11, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - House - Government Judiciary Subcommittee on Immigration and Claims, June 12, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 12, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 12, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Arizona Republic, June 13, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 13, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Tucson Weekly, June 13, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - KOLD.com, June 14, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Papaya-palace.com, June 14, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - KOLD.com, June 14, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 14, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 14, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Green Valley News, June 14, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 15, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 15, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Newsday, June 17, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 17, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 18, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 18, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 18, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 18, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 18, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Green Valley News, June 19, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 19, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 19, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 19, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Arizona Republic, June 19, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 19, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 19, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - El Imparcial, June 20, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Stop the FTAA, July 1, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Arizona Republic, June 20, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 20, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 20, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 20, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 20, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 21, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 21, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 21, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 21, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Noticieros Televisa, June 22, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 23, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 24, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 24, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Benson News-Sun, June 26, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 26, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 27, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Washington Times, June 27, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Yahoo! Noticias, June 27, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Tucson Star, June 27, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - AZCentral.com, June 28, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 29, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Arizona Star, June 29, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 29, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Arizona Republic, July 1, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 1, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Mother Jones, July 2002-August 2002 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 1, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 2, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 2, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Green Valley News, July 3, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Cubaweb, July 3, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 3, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 4, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 4, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Terra.com, July 4, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - VOA News, July 4, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 5, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Green Valley News, July 5, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 5, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 5, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 7, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 7, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 7, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 11, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Radio Unica, July 13, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 13, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 13, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Arizona Republic, July 14, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Arizona Republic, July 14, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Central Christian Church - Springfield, Tennessee, July 14, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 14, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - Arizona Republic, July 14, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - Dallas Morning News, July 15, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - Liloia.com, July 15, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - Salon.com, July 15, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - Cochise Observer, July 15, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 15, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 16, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 17, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 18, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 19, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 20, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 150)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 20, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 20, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 152)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 20, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 153)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 20, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 21, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 155)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 21, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 156)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 22, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 157)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 22, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 158)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 22, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 159)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 22, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 160)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 23, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 22, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 162)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 23, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 163)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 24, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 164)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 24, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 165)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 24, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 166)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 24, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 167)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 24, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 168)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 24, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 169)
    - VDARE, July 25, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 170)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 26, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 171)
    - Dallas News, July 27, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 172)
    - Immigration News Briefs, July 27, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 173)
    - Imperial Valley Press, July 28, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 174)
    - Sierra Vista, July 29, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 175)
    - San Pedro Valley News, July 29, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 176)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 30, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 177)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 30, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 178)
    - Central America/Mexico Report, August 1, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 179)
    - BLM Resource Advisory Council Minutes, August 1, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 180)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 1, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 181)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 1, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 182)
    - National Catholic Reporter, August 2, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 183)
    - National Catholic Reporter, August 2, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 184)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 2, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 185)
    - Denver Post, August 4, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 186)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 5, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 187)
    - Terra.com, August 6, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 188)
    - AZFamily.com, August 6, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 189)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 6, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 190)
    - PC (USA), August 6, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 191)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 6, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 192)
    - The Denver Post, August 7, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 193)
    - FSLF Community News, August 7, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 194)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 8, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 195)
    - Denver Post, August 8, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 196)
    - Washington Post, August 11, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 197)
    - The Holland Sentinel, August 11, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 198)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 11, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 199)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 12, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 200)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 12, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 201)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 12, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 202)
    - The Guardian, August 12, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 203)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 12, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 204)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 12, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 205)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 13, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 206)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 13, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 207)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 14, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 208)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 16, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 209)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 17, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 210)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 17, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 211)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 20, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 212)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 20, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 213)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 20, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 214)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 22, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 215)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 23, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 216)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 23, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 217)
    - Dallas News, August 24, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 218)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 24, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 219)
    - Frontera Hispana, August 26, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 220)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 30, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 221)
    - Mother Jones, September 1, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 222)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 5, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 223)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 11, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 224)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 11, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 225)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 14, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 226)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 14, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 227)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 16, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 228)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 16, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 229)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 16, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 230)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 16, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 231)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 17, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 232)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 17, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 233)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 17, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 234)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 17, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 235)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 18, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 236)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 18, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 237)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 18, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 238)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 18, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 239)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 18, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 240)
    - Los Angeles Times, September 20, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 241)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 19, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 242)
    - Rocky Mountain News, September 21, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 243)
    - Cochise Observer, September 22, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 244)
    - AZIrishmusic.com/news, September 25, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 245)
    - Washington Times, September 26, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 246)
    - El Imparcial, September 27, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 247)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 29, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 248)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 29, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 249)
    - Disciples Justice Action Network, October 1, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 250)
    - The Christian Science Monitor, October 1, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 251)
    - Catholic Vision, October 1, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 252)
    - Gotham Gazette, October 1, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 253)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 3, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 254)
    - Arizona Republic and Tucson Citizen, October 3, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 255)
    - RAC, October 3, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 256)
    - Tucson Citizen, October 3, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 257)
    - Tucson Citizen, October 4, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 258)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 4, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 259)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 4, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 260)
    - El Imparcial, October 5, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 261)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 6, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 262)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 9, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 263)
    - Jim Lehrer Report, October 9, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 264)
    - Tucson Citizen, October 10, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 265)
    - Tucson Citizen, October 10, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 266)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 10, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 267)
    - Tucson Citizen, October 11, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 268)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 16, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 269)
    - Hispanic Vista, October 21, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 270)
    - Frontera NMSU, October 22, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 271)
    - Sharing, October 24, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 272)
    - Tombstone Tumbleweed, October 24, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 273)
    - Weekly News on the Americas, October 24, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 274)
    - Tucson Citizen, October 28, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 275)
    - Bishop’s Migration, October 28, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 276)
    - Enlages News, November 1, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 277)
    - Loaves and Fishes, November 1, 2002 - December 2002 (Box 2, Folder 278)
    - Universidad de Missouri School of Journalism, November 2, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 279)
    - University of Missouri School of Journalism, November 2, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 280)
    - Tucson Citizen, November 5, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 281)
    - El Universal, November 5, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 282)
    - Tucson Citizen, November 6, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 283)
    - Word and World, November 9, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 284)
    - MSNBC News, November 12, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 285)
    - Tucson Citizen, November 14, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 286)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 15, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 287)
    - La Prensa, November 15, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 288)
    - Arizona Daily Wildcat, November 18, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 289)
    - Arizona Daily Wildcat, November 18, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 290)
    - Sierra Vista Herald, November 20, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 291)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 21, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 292)
    - Tucson Citizen, November 25, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 293)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 26, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 294)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 26, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 295)
    - Tucson Citizen, November 30, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 296)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 3, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 297)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 4, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 298)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 5, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 299)
    - Arizona Republic, December 6, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 300)
    - Terra Immigracion, December 6, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 301)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 6, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 302)
    - Terra Turismo, English and Spanish, December 6, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 303)
    - The Arizona Republic, December 8, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 304)
    - Media Monitor, December 9, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 305)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 11, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 306)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 11, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 307)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 16, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 308)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 16, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 309)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 16, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 310)
    - Austin American-Statesman, December 17, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 311)
    - Phoenix ABC 15, December 25, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 312)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 25, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 313)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 26, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 314)
    - LAIC, December 27, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 315)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 28, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 316)
    - Chicago Tribune, December 29, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 317)
    - La Jornada, December 29, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 318)
    - The Round Up, January 9, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - The Arbiter, January 9, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - YCL USA, January 10, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Frontera Hispana, January 20, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Washington Times, January 27, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 28, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 28, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - KOLD - TV, February 13, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 13, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Infocatho, February 15, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Infocatho, February 15, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Tucson Citizen, February 17, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Afghanistan Illegal Surfaces Locally, February 19, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - The Denver Post, February 21, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - VDARE.com, February 21, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Terra Immigracion, February 21, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Rocky Mountain News, February 21, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 21, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - United Church News, March 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Intelligence Report, March 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Tucson Citizen, March 3, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Moscow, The Authorities of the USA are Charged with the Murder of 11 Illegal Immigrants, March 7, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - The Christian Century, March 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 10, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Tucson Citizen, March 11, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Washington Post, March 11, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Prensa Hispana, March 26, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - The New York Times Sao Paulo, March 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Catholic Vision, April 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Presbyterians Today, April 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - The Intelligence Report, April 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Goshen College Service Inquiry Report, April 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Sin Fronteras Center, Death, this is your receipt, April 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - The Intelligence Report, April 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - The Intelligence Report, April 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 6, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Sierra Vista Herald, April 6, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - AZCentral.com, April 7, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Altar, Son. Reposte de la seguna Camina d oracion por los migrantes muertos, April 10, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - San Francisco Bay Area Indymedia, April 11, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Tucson Citizen, April 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - AZCentral.com, April 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - The Arizona Republic, April 17, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - The Arizona Republic, April 17, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Republic Mexico City Bureau, April 18, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - EsMas.com, May 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Intelligence Report SPLC Spring 2003, May 2003 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Arizona Republic, May 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Arizona Republic, May 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 7, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Siskind Immigration Bulletin, May 2, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Arizona Republic, May 5, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 5, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 6, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - La Jornada, May 7, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - World Net Daily, May 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Buchanan and Press, May 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - La Jornada, May 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Proceso.com.mx, May 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - MSNBC, May 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Tucson Citizen, United States sued over border deaths, May 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Silicon Investor, May 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Shotsacrossthebow.com, May 9, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Yuma Sun, May 9, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - The Federal Observer, May 9, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - The Arizona Republic, May 9, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 9, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 9, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Spencer-Buchanan Press American Patrol, May 9, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 10, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - The Arizona Republic, May 10, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 11, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - EFE News Service, May 12, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Siskind’s Immigration Bulletin, May 12, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 13, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 13, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Prensa Hispana, Llevan agua al dsierto de Arizona, May 14, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Denver Post, May 15, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - LA Times, May 15, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 15, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Arizona Republic, Immigrant smugglers like to use big trucks, May 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 18, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - New York Times, May 19, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Arizona Republic, May 20, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Arizona Republic, May 23, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Arizona Daily Star, Letter to Editor Opinion, May 23, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - IRC Communications, The Season of Death, May 23, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 23, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - The Nation, Samaritans in the Desert, May 26, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Washington Post, May 26, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 28, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Arizona Republic, Border beacons help migrants, May 29, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 30, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - The Southern Poverty Law Center, June 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Catholic Vision, Crossing Borders Migrants, June 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - East Bay Sanctuary Covenant Exodus, June 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Arizona Republic, June 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Tombstone Tumbleweed, June 2, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Arizona Daily Star, Matthew Moore dies; church, social activist, June 2, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 2, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Arizona Daily Star, Border militia pledges lifesaving effort, June 3, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 115)